A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station, 1903-1947
Special Collections and University Archives, Virginia Tech
- Series II. Files, 1903-1947
  - Quarterly Bulletin of the Virginia State Crop Pest Commission, v. 1, no. 2 - v. 7, no. 3, 1919 July - 1925 Oct.
    - v. 1, no. 2, Apple Trees/Gall and Woolly Aphis, 1919 July (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - v. 1, no. 3, Green Clover Worm - post of Soy Beans, 1919 Oct. (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - v. 1, no. 4, State Entomologist and Plant Pathologist, 1920 Jan. (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - v. 2, no. 1, Oriental Fruit Moth, 1920 Apr. (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - v. 2, no. 2, Work during Autumn and Spring, 1920-21, 1920 July (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - v. 2, no. 3, Registration of nurseries, 1920 Oct. (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - v. 2, no. 4, Some insects injurious to Alfalfa, 1921 Jan. (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - v. 3, no. 1, Control of spinach leaf mold, 1921 Apr. (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - v. 3, no. 2, Report of inspection work during Autumn of 1920 and Spring of 1921, 1921 July (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - v. 3, no. 3, Nurseries, Natl, 1921 Oct. (Box 97, Folder 12)
    - v. 3, no. 4, State Entomologist and Plant Pathologist, 1922 Jan. (Box 97, Folder 13)
    - v. 4, no. 1, Woolly Aphis, 1922 Apr. (Box 97, Folder 14)
    - v. 4, no. 2, 1922 July (Box 97, Folder 15)
    - v. 4, no. 3, List of registered nurseries, 1922 Oct. (Box 97, Folder 16)
    - v. 4, no. 4, Sweet potatoes, 1923 Jan. (Box 97, Folder 17)
    - v. 5, no. 1, Cedar rust, 1923 Apr. (Box 97, Folder 18)
    - v. 5, no. 2, Treatment of seed corn with tar and paris green, 1923 July (Box 97, Folder 19)
    - v. 5, no. 3, Registered nurseries, 1923 Oct. (Box 97, Folder 20)
    - v. 5, no. 4, 14th report of the State Entomologist and Plant Pathologist, 1924 Jan. (Box 97, Folder 21)
    - v. 6, no. 1, The lesser clover weevil, 1924 Apr. (Box 97, Folder 22)
    - v. 6, no. 2, Recent amendment to crop pest law, 1924 July (Box 97, Folder 23)
    - v. 6, no. 3, List of registered nurseries, 1924 Oct. (Box 97, Folder 24)
    - v. 6, no. 4, Cedar spots and fruit losses, 1925 Jan. (Box 97, Folder 25)
    - v. 7, no. 1, Woolly aphis investigations, 1925 Apr. (Box 97, Folder 26)
    - v. 7, no. 2, The bean beetle in Virginia, 1925 (Box 97, Folder 27)
    - v. 7, no. 3, List of registered nurseries, 1925 Oct. (Box 97, Folder 28)
  - E. borealis spray notes, 1920 (Box 97, Folder 29)
  - Dust Test E. borealis Smithfield, 1921 (Box 97, Folder 30)
  - Sprays, special, for Larvae of Melon Beetle, 1921 (Box 97, Folder 31)
  - Squash Lady-Bird Bugle (original notes from which data was compiled), 1921 (Box 97, Folder 32)
  - E. borealis larvae, 1921 (Box 97, Folder 33)
  - E. borealis Smithfield, VA, 1921 (Box 97, Folder 34)
  - E. borealis, 1920-1921 (Box 97, Folder 35)
  - E. borealis habits, 1921 (Box 97, Folder 36)
  - E. borealis miscellaneous notes (Box 97, Folder 37)
  - Rye Varieties, 1920-1926 (Box 97, Folder 38)
  - Seed Potato Exp., 1920-1927 (Box 97, Folder 39)
  - Woolly Aphis notes by Nickel (experiments at Richmond), 1920 (Box 97, Folder 40)
  - Lime, Rates of applying to corn, Glaussett exper., 1921-1925 (Box 97, Folder 41)
  - Lime Experiment (Box 97, Folder 42)
  - Clipping Exper., 1922-1924 (Box 97, Folder 43)
  - Hay, 1922-1923 (Box 97, Folder 44)
  - Insecticides, Chemical Examination of - E. L. Andrews, Jr., 1922 (Box 97, Folder 45)
  - Lysimeter, 1922-1923 (Box 97, Folder 46)
  - Lysimeter Results, 1922-1923 (Box 97, Folder 47)
  - Lysimeter Experiments (new year began on 8-30-23), 1923-1924 (Box 97, Folder 48)
  - Lysimeter Experiments, 1924-1925 (Box 97, Folder 49)
  - Lysimeter Experiments, VA-Tenn., 1924-1925 (Box 97, Folder 50)
  - Lysimeter Experiments, 1925-1926 (Box 97, Folder 51)
  - Lysimeter Experiments (old exp.), 1925-1926 (Box 97, Folder 52)
  - Lysimeter Results (alkalines and nitrates), 1926-1927 (Box 97, Folder 53)
  - Lysimeter Experiments, VA-Tenn., 4th year, 1927-1928 (Box 97, Folder 54)
  - Lysimeter Experiments, VA 6th year, 1927-1928 (Box 97, Folder 55)
  - Lysimeter Experiments, VA, 1928-1930 (Box 97, Folder 56)
  - Lysimeter Results, VA-Tenn., 1928-1930 (Box 97, Folder 57)
  - Lysimeter Experiments, VA, 1929-1930 (Box 97, Folder 58)
  - Lysimeter Results, (VA & VA-Tenn.), 1930-1931 (Box 97, Folder 59)
  - Peach Moth, Oriental, Inspection report, 1922 (Box 97, Folder 60)
  - Spreader Tests at Winchester, 1922 (Box 97, Folder 61)
  - Tobacco Experiment Project, 1922 (Box 97, Folder 62)
  - Miscellaneous, 1922-1924 (Box 97, Folder 63)
  - Orchard Grass Exp., 1923-1927 (Box 97, Folder 64)
  - Red Clover Exper., 1923-1926 (Box 97, Folder 65)
  - Red Clover Project, 1926-1928 (Box 97, Folder 66)
  - Entomology Dept., notes of W. S. Hough, 1924 (Box 97, Folder 67)
  - Potatoes, 1918 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Potato Varieties Project (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Spraying, 1918 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Chemistry-Composting, 1919 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Hutcheson, Prof. T.B., 1919 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Orchard, Experimental, Planted near Veterinary Building, 1919 (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - Sulphur Experiment (results & notes), 1919 (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 98, Folder 8-9)
  - Budget Requests, 1922-1924 (Box 98, Folder 10)
  - Budget Requests, VAES Depts., 1928-1930 (Box 98, Folder 11)
  - Budget, 1930-1932 (Box 98, Folder 12)
  - Budget Estimates, 1930-1932 (Box 98, Folder 13)
  - Budget Requests, all depts. combined, 1931-1932 (Box 98, Folder 14)
  - Budget Requests, 1930-1931 (Box 98, Folder 15)
  - Budget Estimates, 1932-1934 (Box 98, Folder 16)
  - Budget Requests, VAES Depts., 1932-1934 (Box 98, Folder 17)
  - Budget, 1935-1936 (Box 98, Folder 18)
  - Budget Requests, 1934-1936 (Box 98, Folder 19)
  - Budget Requests, 1936-1938 (Box 98, Folder 20-21)
  - Allotment Estimates for, 1937-1938 (Box 98, Folder 22)
  - Expenditures, Estimated for June (Box 98, Folder 23)
  - Labor Payrolls, 1936-1937 (Box 98, Folder 24)
  - Labor Vouchers, Departmental, 1937-1938 (Box 98, Folder 25)
  - Payroll Vouchers, 1936-1937 (Box 98, Folder 26)
  - President's Statement to BOV, 1935 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Revenue Slips (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Revenue Slips, 1937-1938 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Salary Payrolls, 1936-1937 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Salary Payrolls, 1937 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Salary Payrolls, 1937-1938 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - TVA Vouchers and Payrolls, 1937-1938 (Box 99, Folder 7-8)
  - Budget Requests, 1936-1938 (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - Expenditures, Estimated, Deptl., 1936 (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - Labor Payrolls, 1934-1935 (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - Payroll, Labor, 1935-1936 (Box 99, Folder 12)
  - Payrolls, Salary, 1935-1936 (Box 99, Folder 13)
  - Regional Adjustment in Farming, 1935 (Box 99, Folder 14)
  - Revenues, 1936 (Box 99, Folder 15)
  - Vouchers, Labor, 1936 (Box 99, Folder 16)
  - Tennessee Valley Authority (TVA), A. L. Grizzard, 1936 (Box 99, Folder 17)
  - Flea Beetle, Pale-Striped, Richmond - G.W. Underhill, 1924-1925 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Woolly Aphis Investigations by G.W. Underhill, 1924-1926 (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - Clover Experiments, 1925-1928 (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Crop Pest Reports on Time Distribution, 1925-1926 (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - Grain Moth - C. Swoope, 1925 (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - Tuber Moth, 1925 (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - Euonymus Scale in Virginia by G.W. Underhill, 1925-1926 (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - Woolly Aphis, Apple, Notes by G.W. Underhill, 1925 (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - Woolly Aphis - Apple, 1926 (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - Apple Nursery Stock, Paradichlorobenzine, tests on, Richmond - G.W. Underhill, 1926 (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - Barred Rock Reactors, 1926-1927 (Box 100, Folder 11)
  - Cagle, L.R., Annual Report of Investigations, 1926 (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - Cagle, L.R., Annual Report of Investigations, 1927 (Box 100, Folder 13)
  - Cagle, L.R., Scratch Report, 1927 (Box 100, Folder 14)
  - Cagle, L.R., Annual Report of Investigations, 1928 (Box 100, Folder 15)
  - Cagle, L.R., Annual Report, 1928 (Box 100, Folder 16)
  - Cagle, L.R., Scratch Report, 1928 (Box 100, Folder 17)
  - Cagle, L.R., Report, 1930 (Box 100, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 100, Folder 19)
  - Cagle's. Mr., Report Section III, 1931 (Box 100, Folder 20)
  - Cagle's, L.R., Life History Notes, 1932 (Box 100, Folder 21)
  - Cagle's, L.R., Report-Part, 1932 (Box 100, Folder 22)
  - Dr. A.W. Drinkard, Jr., Director, correspondence files, 1925-1926
    - A Miscellaneous, 1925-1926 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - B Miscellaneous (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Burruss, Pres. Julian A., Exec. Bulletins, 1925-1926 (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - C Miscellaneous (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Clubs, VPI, 1925 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - D Miscellaneous (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - E Miscellaneous (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - F Miscellaneous (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - G Miscellaneous (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - H Miscellaneous (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - I Miscellaneous (Box 101, Folder 11)
    - J Miscellaneous (Box 101, Folder 12)
    - K Miscellaneous (Box 101, Folder 13)
    - L Miscellaneous, 1926 (Box 101, Folder 14)
    - M Miscellaneous, 1926 (Box 101, Folder 15)
    - N Miscellaneous, 1926 (Box 101, Folder 16)
    - O Miscellaneous, 1926 (Box 101, Folder 17)
    - O'Neill, C.T. (Box 101, Folder 18)
    - P Miscellaneous, 1926 (Box 101, Folder 19)
    - Price, E.R., editor (Box 101, Folder 20)
    - Price, Dean H.L. (Box 101, Folder 21)
    - Q-R Miscellaneous, 1926 (Box 101, Folder 22)
    - Reynolds, Dr. Ellen A., 1925-1926 (Box 101, Folder 23)
    - Richards, H.I., 1924-1925 (Box 101, Folder 24)
    - Runnells, R.A. (Box 101, Folder 25)
    - Russell, E.Z. (Box 101, Folder 26)
    - S Miscellaneous, 1926 (Box 101, Folder 27)
    - Schneideran, F.J., 1925-1926 (Box 101, Folder 28)
    - Schoene, W.J., 1925-1926 (Box 101, Folder 29)
    - Seitz, Prof. Chas. E. (Box 101, Folder 30)
    - Sheets, E.W., 1925-1926 (Box 101, Folder 31)
    - Smith, A.G., Jr., 1925-1926 (Box 101, Folder 32)
    - Spencer, D.A., 1924-1925 (Box 101, Folder 33)
    - Strawn, O.P., 1925-1926 (Box 101, Folder 34)
    - T Miscellaneous, 1926 (Box 101, Folder 35)
    - Taylor, C.C., 1925-1926 (Box 101, Folder 36)
    - Taylor, Henry M., 1925-1926 (Box 101, Folder 37)
    - Thomas, Arthur H., Co. (Box 101, Folder 38)
    - Thomas Publishing Co. (Box 101, Folder 39)
    - Tolley, H.R., 1925 (Box 101, Folder 40)
    - Trinkle, Hon. E. Lee, Gov., 1925-1926 (Box 101, Folder 41)
    - U-V Miscellaneous, 1926 (Box 101, Folder 42)
    - Vernon, J.J. (Box 101, Folder 43)
    - Wingard, S.A. (Box 101, Folder 44)
    - Wolfe, Dr. T.K. (Box 101, Folder 45)
    - W-X-Y-Z Miscellaneous, 1926 (Box 101, Folder 46)
  - Coccidiosis Coop Testing, 1926-1927 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Codling Moth, 1926 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Codling Moth, 1929 (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Codling Moth, Life History Studies at Hollins, 1930 (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - Codling Moth and Peach Moth, Laboraatory data on, Hollins and Blacksburg, 1936 (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - Codling Moth, Thesis, E.L. Wood, 1939 (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - Codling Moth Records, 1940 (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - Green Soldier Bug, Preliminiary report by G.W. Underhill, 1926 (Box 102, Folder 8)
  - Phosphate/Green Manure Exper., 1926 (Box 102, Folder 9)
  - Serum Dilution, 1926 (Box 102, Folder 10)
  - Sodium Fluosilicate on Diabrotica Beetles by G.W. Underhill, 1926 (Box 102, Folder 11)
  - Crop Rotations, Theory, 1927 (Box 102, Folder 12)
  - Leafhopper Studies, 1927 (Box 102, Folder 13)
  - Leafhopper Life History Notes, 1928 (Box 102, Folder 14)
  - Leafhopper Figures and Charts, Prof Schoene's ms., 1928 (Box 102, Folder 15)
  - Leafhopper Life History Notes, 1928 (Box 102, Folder 16)
  - Leafhopper Investigations, 1929 (Box 102, Folder 17-18)
  - Leafhopper Investigations, W.J. Schoene, 1930 (Box 102, Folder 19-20)
  - Leafhopper Field Notes, 1930 (Box 102, Folder 21)
  - Leafhopper Notes (Sprays), scratch copy on part of, 1930 (Box 102, Folder 22)
  - Leafhopper Field and Lab Notes, W.J. Schoene, 1931 (Box 102, Folder 23)
  - Leafhopper Field and Laboratory Notes, 1931 (Box 102, Folder 24)
  - Leafhopper Notes, 1931 (Box 102, Folder 25)
  - Leafhopper Field and Lab Notes, 1932 (Box 102, Folder 26)
  - Leafhopper Notes Insectary, 1932 (Box 102, Folder 27)
  - Leafhopper Field Notes, 1932 (Box 102, Folder 28)
  - Leafhopper Notes, 1934-1936 (Box 102, Folder 29)
  - Leafhopper Project Notes, 1942 (Box 102, Folder 30)
  - Thorp, Frank, Jr., Contamination Tests, 1926 (Box 102, Folder 31)
  - Mint Exper., 1928 (Box 102, Folder 32)
  - Richmond Field Lab - Misc. Notes by G.W. Underhill, 1928 (Box 102, Folder 33)
  - Trichogramma Notes, 1929 (Box 102, Folder 34)
  - Pasture Grass Data, Series A amd B, 1928-1938 (Box 102, Folder 35)
  - Nitrate of Soda, 1929-1930 (Box 102, Folder 36)
  - Soil Samples - T.W Sibold, 1929 (Box 102, Folder 37)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, 1929, 1932 (Box 102, Folder 38)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, 1930-1931 (Box 102, Folder 39)
  - Dr. A.W. Drinkard, Jr., Director, correspondence files, 1926-1927
    - Box content list (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - Allen, E.W. (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Anderson, B.G. (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Andrews, F.S. (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Apperson, Kent (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Auchter, Prof. E.G. (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Austin, V.C. (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Bargamin, Russell (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - Barger, Capt. D.H. (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - Barnett, J.E. (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - Barre, H.M. (Box 103, Folder 11)
    - Barry, Mrs Maggie W. (Box 103, Folder 12)
    - Bell Company, J.P. (Box 103, Folder 13)
    - Bradford, J.H. (Box 103, Folder 14)
    - Brown-Morrison Co. (Box 103, Folder 15)
    - Burmeister, C.A. (Box 103, Folder 16)
    - Butler, G.F., Gen. Freight Agent (Box 103, Folder 17)
    - Byrd, Governor Harry F. (Box 103, Folder 18)
    - Caldwell-Sites Co. (Box 103, Folder 19)
    - Central Chemical Co. (Box 103, Folder 20)
    - Chilean Nitrate of Soda (Box 103, Folder 21)
    - Chrisman, Dr. W.G. (Box 103, Folder 22)
    - Cocke, R.P. (Box 103, Folder 23)
    - Cooper, M.R. (Box 103, Folder 24)
    - Copley, T.L. (Box 103, Folder 25)
    - Dean, AL. (Box 103, Folder 26)
    - Ellett, Dr. W.B. (Box 103, Folder 27)
    - Eoff, M.H. (Box 103, Folder 28)
    - Ezekiel, M. (Box 103, Folder 29)
    - Farmer, W.J. (Box 103, Folder 30)
    - Fogelman, J.B. (Box 103, Folder 31)
    - Fromme, Dr. F.D. (Box 103, Folder 32)
    - Garnett, Dr. W.E. (Box 103, Folder 33)
    - H Miscellaneous (Box 103, Folder 34)
    - Haskins, C.B. (Box 103, Folder 35)
    - Heitshu, D.C. (Box 103, Folder 36)
    - Hofman, Dr. F.W. (Box 103, Folder 37)
    - Holdway, Prof. C.W. (Box 103, Folder 38)
    - Hough, W.S. (Box 103, Folder 39)
    - Hunt, R.E. (Box 103, Folder 40)
    - Hurt, R.H. (Box 103, Folder 41)
    - Hutcheson, John R. (Box 103, Folder 42)
    - Hutcheson, T.B. (Box 103, Folder 43)
    - Hutson, J.B. (Box 103, Folder 44)
    - I Miscellaneous (Box 103, Folder 45)
    - J Miscellaneous (Box 103, Folder 46)
    - Jardine, Hon. W.M. (Box 103, Folder 47)
    - Johnson, T.C. (Box 103, Folder 48)
    - K Miscellaneous (Box 103, Folder 49)
    - Koiner, Hon. C.W. (Box 103, Folder 50)
    - L Miscellaneous (Box 103, Folder 51)
    - Langsford, E.L. (Box 103, Folder 52)
    - Lupton, Mcsherry (Box 103, Folder 53)
    - M Miscellaneous (Box 103, Folder 54)
    - Mc Miscellaneous (Box 103, Folder 55)
    - McCall, Dr. A.G. (Box 103, Folder 56)
    - Magill, E.C. (Box 103, Folder 57)
    - Meek, J.H. (Box 103, Folder 58)
    - Michell, H.F., Company (Box 103, Folder 59)
    - Miller, E.C. (Box 103, Folder 60)
    - Moore, RC. (Box 103, Folder 61)
    - Moore, The Lime Co. (Box 103, Folder 62)
    - Murphy, Louis S. (Box 103, Folder 63)
    - National Research Council (Box 103, Folder 64)
    - N Miscellaneous (Box 103, Folder 65)
    - Nobles, C.R. (Box 103, Folder 66)
    - O Miscellaneous (Box 103, Folder 67)
    - P Miscellaneous (Box 103, Folder 68)
    - Pettinger, N.A. (Box 103, Folder 69)
    - Pollard, Dr. John Garland (Box 103, Folder 70)
    - Price, E.R. (Box 103, Folder 71)
    - Price, H.L., Dean (Box 103, Folder 72)
    - Printing Dept., VPI (Box 103, Folder 73)
    - Programs (Box 103, Folder 74)
    - R Miscellaneous (Box 103, Folder 75)
    - Reynolds, Dr. Ellen A. (Box 103, Folder 76)
    - Roanoke Glass Co. (Box 103, Folder 77)
    - Roudabush, T.A. (Box 103, Folder 78)
    - S Miscellaneous (Box 103, Folder 79)
    - Schneiderhan, F.J. (Box 103, Folder 80)
    - Schoene, Prof. W.J. (Box 103, Folder 81)
    - Sheets, E.W. (Box 103, Folder 82)
    - State Farmer's Institute (Box 103, Folder 83)
    - Snavely, Dr. T.R. (Box 103, Folder 84)
    - Stark Bro's Nurseries and Orchard Co. (Box 103, Folder 85)
    - Stechert, G.E., and Co. (Box 103, Folder 86)
    - Strong, W.O. (Box 103, Folder 87)
    - Supt of Documents (Box 103, Folder 88)
    - Swinson, Carl R. (Box 103, Folder 89)
    - T Miscellaneous (Box 103, Folder 90)
    - Thomas, Arthur H. Co. (Box 103, Folder 91)
    - Thorpe, Dr. Frank, Jr. (Box 103, Folder 92)
    - U Miscellaneous (Box 103, Folder 93)
    - Underwood Typewriter Co. (Box 103, Folder 94)
    - U.S. Dept. of Agriculture (Box 103, Folder 95)
    - U.S. Dept. of Commerce (Box 103, Folder 96)
    - U.S. Dept of Labor (Box 103, Folder 97)
    - Universities (Box 103, Folder 98)
    - V Miscellaneous (Box 103, Folder 99)
    - Vernon, J.J. (Box 103, Folder 100)
    - VA Agricultural Experiment Statement (Box 103, Folder 101)
    - Virginia Seed Service (Box 103, Folder 102)
    - W Miscellaneous (Box 103, Folder 103)
    - Wade, Charles I., Treas. (Box 103, Folder 104)
    - Wolfe, T.K. (Box 103, Folder 105)
    - Wood, Col. T. Gilbert (Box 103, Folder 106)
    - Y Miscellaneous (Box 103, Folder 107)
  - Shenandoah Valley, 1926 (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Winchester - Apple Insect Investigations, 1927 (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Winchester - Apple Insect Investigations - W.S. Hough, 1928 (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - Winchester, 1929 (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Winchester, 1930 (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Winchester, 1931 (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Winchester, 1932 (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Winchester, 1933 (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - Winchester, 1934 (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - Winchester, 1935 (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - Winchester, 1936 (Box 104, Folder 11)
  - Winchester, 1937 (Box 104, Folder 12)
  - Winchester, 1938 (Box 104, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous, 1939 (Box 104, Folder 14)
  - Winchester, 1940 (Box 104, Folder 15)
  - Winchester, 1941 (Box 104, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous, 1943 (Box 104, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous, 1944 (Box 104, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous, 1945 (Box 104, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous, 1946 (Box 104, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous, 1947 (Box 104, Folder 21)
  - Winchester, 1949 (Box 104, Folder 22)
  - Winchester - W.S. Hough, 1949 (Box 104, Folder 23)
  - Dr. A.W. Drinkard, Jr., Director, correspondence files, 1927-1928
    - Box content list (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - A Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - Administrative Council, VPI (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Allen, E.W., 1927-1928 (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - Allwood, Prof W.B., 1927 (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - American Fertilizer, The (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - Anderson, B.G., 1927-1928 (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - Applications, 1925-1928 (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - B Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 105, Folder 9-10)
    - Bailey, Miss Ilena M., 1927-1928 (Box 105, Folder 11)
    - Ballinger, Roy A, 1927-1928 (Box 105, Folder 12)
    - Bradford, J.H., 1927-1928 (Box 105, Folder 13)
    - Bertha Mineral Co. (Box 105, Folder 14)
    - Brodell, AP. (Box 105, Folder 15)
    - Brown, Ralph M., 1927-1928 (Box 105, Folder 16)
    - Brown-Morrison Co. (Box 105, Folder 17)
    - Burruss, Pres. Julian A., 1927-1928 (Box 105, Folder 18)
    - Burrows Fidding Machine Co. (Box 105, Folder 19)
    - Byrd, Gov. Harry Flood, 1927-1928 (Box 105, Folder 20)
    - C Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 105, Folder 21)
    - Caldwell - Sites Co. (Box 105, Folder 22)
    - Central Scientific Co. (Box 105, Folder 23)
    - Combs, E.R., Comptroller [State], 1927-1928 (Box 105, Folder 24)
    - Conner, Prof W.G., 1927-1928 (Box 105, Folder 25)
    - D Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 105, Folder 26)
    - Dinwidde, Martha (Box 105, Folder 27)
    - Drinkard, AW., Jr., 1927-1928 (Box 105, Folder 28)
    - E Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 105, Folder 29)
    - Ellett, Dr. W.B. (Box 105, Folder 30)
    - Eimer & Amena (Box 105, Folder 31)
    - Extension Division (Box 105, Folder 32)
    - F Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 105, Folder 33)
    - Farrar, Thomas J. (Box 105, Folder 34)
    - Felt & Tarrant Mfg. Co. (Box 105, Folder 35)
    - Ferguson, Senator S.L. (Box 105, Folder 36)
    - Fibre Board Container Co. (Box 105, Folder 37)
    - Finance and Executive (Box 105, Folder 38)
    - Fogelman, J.B. (Box 105, Folder 39)
    - Fromme, Dr. F.D. (Box 105, Folder 40)
    - Funchess, M.J. (Box 105, Folder 41)
    - G Miscellaneous (Box 105, Folder 42)
    - Gandy, Pres. J.M. (Box 105, Folder 43)
    - Gardener, V.R. (Box 105, Folder 44)
    - Garnett, Dr. W.E. (Box 105, Folder 45)
    - Giles, Dr. Albert W. (Box 105, Folder 46)
    - Glass, Hon. Carter (Box 105, Folder 47)
    - Glassett, Mrs. F.S. (Box 105, Folder 48)
    - Gray, Dan T., Dean & Director (Box 105, Folder 49)
    - Green, W.W. (Box 105, Folder 50)
    - Griffin, Chas. E., Co., Inc. (Box 105, Folder 51)
    - Gudheim, Prof H. (Box 105, Folder 52)
    - Hankins, O.G. (Box 105, Folder 53)
    - Hildreth, AC. (Box 105, Folder 54)
    - Hodges, LeRoy (Box 105, Folder 55)
    - Holdaway, Prof C.W. (Box 105, Folder 56)
    - Horsley, J.R. (Box 105, Folder 57)
    - Hough, W.S. (Box 105, Folder 58)
    - Hutcheson, Jno. R., Director (Box 105, Folder 59)
    - Hutcheson, Prof T.B. (Box 105, Folder 60)
    - James, B.O. (Box 105, Folder 61)
    - Johnson, Prof T.C. (Box 105, Folder 62)
    - Koiner, G.W. (Box 105, Folder 63)
    - Kuttroff, Pickharat & Co., Inc. (Box 105, Folder 64)
    - Langsford, E.L. (Box 105, Folder 65)
    - Loucks, Nelson A (Box 105, Folder 66)
    - Magill, E.C. (Box 105, Folder 67)
    - Meek, J.H. (Box 105, Folder 68)
    - Miller, E.C. (Box 105, Folder 69)
    - Moore, R.C. (Box 105, Folder 70)
    - Moore Lime Co., The (Box 105, Folder 71)
    - Nelson, R.F. (Box 105, Folder 72)
    - Nobles, C.R. (Box 105, Folder 73)
    - Printing Dept., VPI (Box 105, Folder 74)
    - Virginia Seed Service (Box 105, Folder 75)
    - Wade, Chas I., Treas (Box 105, Folder 76)
    - Wood, Col. T.G. (Box 105, Folder 77)
    - Whalin, C.V. (Box 105, Folder 78)
    - Wilcox, R.H. (Box 105, Folder 79)
    - Wilkinson, Frank B. (Box 105, Folder 80)
    - Wilson, Dr. I.D. (Box 105, Folder 81)
  - Staunton Field Lab, 1927 (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Staunton Field Lab, 1928 (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Staunton Field Lab, 1929 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Staunton Field Lab, 1930 (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - Staunton Field Lab, 1931 (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - Staunton Field Lab, 1932 (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Staunton Field Lab, 1933 (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - Staunton Field Lab, 1934 (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - Staunton Field Lab, 1935 (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - Staunton Field Lab, 1936 (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - Staunton Field Lab, 1937 (Box 106, Folder 11)
  - Staunton Field Lab, 1938 (Box 106, Folder 12)
  - Staunton Field Lab, 1939 (Box 106, Folder 13)
  - Staunton Field Lab, 1940 (Box 106, Folder 14)
  - Staunton Field Lab, 1941 (Box 106, Folder 15)
  - Staunton Field Lab, 1942 (Box 106, Folder 16)
  - Staunton Field Lab, 1943 (Box 106, Folder 17)
  - Staunton Field Lab, 1944 (Box 106, Folder 18)
  - Staunton Field Lab, 1945 (Box 106, Folder 19-20)
  - Staunton Field Lab, 1949 (Box 106, Folder 21)
  - Underhill, G.W., Report, 1927 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Underhill, G.W., Report, 1928 (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Underhill, G.W., Report, 1929 (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - Underhill, G.W., Report, 1930 (Box 107, Folder 4)